Placeholder context for project details
\nBug fix implementation: Button would close page on click. Fix implemented to allow button to open expected modal.


New massive upgrade for the button. Going forward this button will open a modal with a form for the user to fill out. This will allow the user to submit a request for a new feature or report a bug. This will be a great way to keep track of user feedback and improve the application.
